[Love in Pavilion]
[Episode 2]
Brothers, take the lady out first.
Then what about him?
Ignorant boy.
You think this is enough
to break my poison formation?
Dream on!
There's actually
such a mighty prodigy from the human race.
You've made me think twice about killing a talent like you.
I'll let you leave.
I came for the Hundred-Eyed Demon Lord's demon core.
I won't leave empty-handed.
I heard what you said
at the Star-Picking Tower.
Isn't it just that the Yiqi Alliance wants to attack Nanchui?
Let them come!
I won't let anyone take away
my nephew's demon core.
Are you trying to protect your relative
and let thousands of little demons in Nanchui die for it, Demon King?
So what?
The Nangongs
won't benefit from it either.
Forsaking emotions, pursuing hatred; eternal night befalls.
Sir, you know this prophecy
is warning both humans and demons
to pull themselves back from the brink
and stop fighting each other.
I've only been in seclusion for a year,
and you just caused such a big disaster.
Get back there now!
Does the promise you made to me earlier
still stand?
I'll add one more condition.
If I get your demon core,
I promise I'll try my best to save Nanchui
and make Nangong Ye pay the price.
Good!
Very good.
You little dummy,
I'll protect you.
So you have nothing to fear.
Uncle, you should protect
those demons like Lady Poison's people,
who have no desire to kill
and only want to lead
a peaceful life in Nanchui.
Let me go.
♪The soul wandering in destiny♪
♪It melts in your♪
♪Gentle gaze♪
♪I trace your silhouette with my fingertips♪
♪Reduced into ashes♪
♪I'm still looking for you♪
♪I used to be like the wind, searching♪
♪Every nook and cranny♪
♪And I was once like water, asking♪
It was my fault
♪Every lake♪
♪I swallow the growing thorns♪
to act recklessly.
♪Lost in love's bitter toll♪
But I sought revenge for Lady Poison
♪Yet I heard the pulse♪
and built this Star-Picking Tower.
♪Letting everything rise from the void♪
I did nothing wrong.
♪Making the sun and moon vanish from obsession♪
♪And love drowns me♪
I don't regret it.
♪In the fatal ecstasy♪
♪If I turn into a poisonous thorn apple♪
♪Lurking in the dark♪
♪If I can look♪
♪Into your eyes, lingering♪
♪And falling♪
♪The soul wandering in destiny♪
♪It melts in your♪
Demon Lord!
♪Gentle gaze♪
Demon Lord...
My dear.
♪I trace your silhouette with my fingertips♪
I want you to live well
♪Reduced into ashes♪
in your new home.
♪I'm still looking for you♪
♪I was once like a stubborn flower♪
♪Blooming in the desert♪
♪The withered grass extinguished♪
♪The flames of the eternal night♪
♪The thorns all over the body illuminate♪
Demon Lord...
♪Love's bitter toll♪
♪Piercing through all the tenderness♪
♪Letting everything rise from the void♪
♪Making the sun and moon vanish from obsession♪
♪And love drowns me♪
♪In the fatal ecstasy♪
♪If I turn into a poisonous thorn apple♪
♪Lurking in the dark♪
♪If I can look♪
♪Into your eyes, lingering♪
♪Letting everything rise from the void♪
♪Making the sun and moon vanish from obsession♪
♪And love drowns me♪
♪In the fatal ecstasy♪
♪If I turn into a poisonous thorn apple♪
♪Lurking in the dark♪
♪If I can look♪
He has already paid for his sins.
♪Into your eyes, lingering♪
You can take him to cultivate over again
and turn over a new leaf.
♪And falling♪
His last wish was for you
to live well.
Demon Lord,
I'm willing to keep you company while cultivating for another thousand years.
-Huaizhu!
-I didn't even use this one.
Look at Miss Dongfang.
Huaizhu,
did you crack that hard nut, the Hundred-Eyed Demon Lord?
How did you make it?
Did you get into any trouble?
Not just the Hundred-Eyed Demon Lord!
We also ran into the Nanchui Poison King,
Huandu Qingtian, a Great Demon King-level figure
with three thousand years of cultivation.
As the so-called invincible Huandu,
he still got
beaten up by us, huh?
That's exaggerated.
It could count as a draw.
Did you get hurt?
Was it a hero saving a beauty in danger,
or a beauty saving a hero?
Miss, you must be tired.
Would you like some water?
Let me fetch it for Huaizhu.
You go give it to her.
You've been poisoned.
Come with me.
Hmm, fishy.
You've inhaled too much
of the Poison King's toxic mist.
Take the pill in it,
work your energy for 15 minutes, and you'll be fine.
Your scabbard.
Actually, miss, your spiritual fire can neutralize poison.
You didn't need my protection at all.
I was kind of cocky asking you to stay
within 10 steps away from me.
Alright,
let me return this to its owner.
I should take my leave now.
Thank you, miss.
Take care.
Qinlan,
let's go.
[Bamboo Pavilion by River Huai]
[On July 7th, Bamboo Pavilion by River Huai]
On July 7th, see you
at the Bamboo Pavilion by River Huai.
See you there.
Poison King,
are you really letting them go so easily like this?
They are helping Nanchui.
The sword from the Wangquans,
the fire from the Dongfangs.
Perhaps the status quo is really going to change drastically.
The Divine Fire did show up here.
But the Wangquan Sword? Where?
Although he used a trick
to hide his identity with a different sword technique,
it couldn't fool my eyes.
It's time
for Old Nangong to pay
for all his evil deeds.
Hurry! Move quickly!
Hurry up! Run!
Come on!
Run!
Quickly!
Hurry!
Run faster!
Sister...
Run!
Run! Now!
Sister!
Go!
Release my sister!
Sister!
You can come at me!
But leave my little sister alone!
I guess you must be feeling terrible right now.
We, the Nangong family, caught you
to extract your demon cores for sword forging.
But not every lowly demon
is qualified for this.
We want the strongest
and the most stubborn ones
with the deepest resentment.
I hope you all die a horrible death!
Your resentment is still not enough.
Don't touch my little sister! Come at me!
Let go of my sister!
Sister!
Sister...
Help!
I won't let you off even if I die!
That's enough now.
You did it!
Who's there?
Sister...
Sister, sister.
Your master is so brutal.
Why don't you try to stab him too?
Good boy.
Who are you?
How dare you ruin our Nangong family's plan?
Oh, the famous Nangong family!
I'm so scared!
[Wangquan Zui from Mask Group]
[Yang Yitan from Mask Group]
I was wondering who it was.
Turns out to be you two bitches from the Mask Group.
What are you waiting for?
Kill them!
Take 3 steps to the left; slash to the right.
Block the left side with your sword; take a step back; move to the right.
Dodge.
Yitan, are you really just talking and doing nothing?
Yes, since you're so capable.
You good-for-nothings!
Get them!
You didn't do it like you said, Yitan.
I had already held back.
Didn't expect you to have the guts to attack us while we were not looking.
Surprised, huh?
[Sky-breaking Temple]
Hongye.
Hongye!
[On July 7th, Bamboo Pavilion by River Huai]
My son, Hongye.
This tree feeds on hatred.
Forsaking emotions, pursuing hatred; eternal night befalls.
There will be no peace in the world.
Hongye,
[Wangquan Shouzhuo, Master of Wangquan Manor, Yiqi Alliance]
you must remember my words.
Stop the conflict between humans and demons
and prevent the eternal night from befalling.
It was that dream again.
I've been having
the same dream repeatedly for 3 years.
[Wangquan Hongye from Wangquan Party of Yiqi Alliance]
It took a month
and consumed countless spiritual stones.
What's the use?
This top can gather the energy in the world
and spin for a month by itself.
How's it? Can you make it?
Useless.
And ugly too.
Sorry, I'm late.
I'll make it up with delicious food and drinks.
Here.
Char siu from Yunhe Tower.
Vegetarian cakes from Su Jin Ji.
-And desserts from Huayun Pavilion.
-I want this.
Hongye, come out.
-It's your favorite date-paste cake!
-Delicious.
This is the map of Nangong Sword Furnace.
After nightfall.
the Xuanyin Formation will be activated outside the Sword Furnace
with no guards.
To break this formation,
you need to move in person.
[Divine Fire Villa, Yiqi Alliance]
There's no way!
This one!
How's that? You're out of cards, aren't you?
I'm as still and solid as a mountain.
I'll shatter you with my wind-riding technique.
[Visiting Card]
The Dark-Sword Zhang family
is a nemesis of your Ji family's wind-riding technique.
How about that? You lost, huh?
You're out of cards, right?
How come the Zhang family also came to visit you, Father?
[Dongfang Churi, Father of Huaizhu and Qinlan, Master of Divine Fire Villa, Yiqi Alliance]
The Zhang family didn't come for a marriage proposal.
Then I'll have to...
The Mask Group Leader, your nemesis!
[Visiting Card]
Qinlan,
well...
The Mask Group Leader?
Who is this?
There's no such a card!
Besides,
the Dark Sword is known as the second-strongest sword in the Yiqi Alliance.
This so-called
Mask Group Leader.
how could he be my nemesis?
Unless you have a visiting card from the Wangquan family.
You don't understand.
My sister never cares about the worldly things.
She's aloof to outsiders.
How could she possibly like these noble family members?
You're right.
But Huaizhu has feelings
for this Mask Group Leader.
Well,
Huaizhu has feelings for him,
or he has feelings for Huaizhu?
Curious?
Then admit defeat.
If you admit defeat, I'll tell you the story
of how Huaizhu met the chosen one
while we went up the mountain to gather herbs.
Come on, stick it, stick it.
And tell me the story once you're done.
Stick it here.
What are you doing?
Well, um...
The matchmakers flooded in again.
They all came
for your Demon-Slaying Fire.
That doesn't mean
you can play their visiting cards.
We did this
to criticize them.
Qinlan's right.
We were criticizing them!
Look at all this
motley crew with fishy intentions.
Ignore them.
Yeah.
Out! All of them!
So, Qinlan,
have you done your abacus practice today?
Father,
have you taken your medicine today?
I'm hungry. Isn't it time to eat?
Let me clean this up.
Let me do it.
Leave these tiring chores to me.
I'll do it.
I want to act like a good daughter.
You can forget about it.
Qinlan can move today's abacus practice to tomorrow,
but Father can't miss his medicine today.
I'll go bring it to you.
Good medicine tastes bitter, but it works.
Uncle Churi,
please let Zhu rest assured.
Yang!
[Yang Yan, the Clairvoyant Yang Family of Yiqi Alliance]
[Wangquan Manor, Yiqi Alliance]
[Unparalleled Sword]
Young Master.
Those heads of noble families
are waiting in the meeting hall.
They seem to be here with ill intentions.
[Unparalleled Sword]
Any news of my father recently?
No.
Nangong Ye seems to be getting suspicious as well.
He doubts that our master is not traveling out there
as we claimed.
[Unparalleled Sword]
That's why they're getting more and more rampant now.
The Nangong family is growing stronger.
Be careful, Young Master, he might be planning to seize power.
[Meeting Hall, Wangquan Manor]
-Young Master Wangquan!
[Gu Henian, Master of Gu Family, Yiqi Alliance]
[Cheng Ling, Master of Cheng Family, Yiqi Alliance]
[Zhang Zheng, Master of Zhang Family, Yiqi Alliance]
Young Master Wangquan,
everyone here is one of our own.
So no beating around the bush then.
Young Master, when will you issue an order
to have all the clans attack Nanchui?
[Yiqi Alliance]
The Alliance Leader's token is here.
Master Nangong, issue your order now.
The Yiqi Alliance
is led by Wangquan Manor.
You're in charge of everything for now, Young Master.
How could I overstep my bounds?
Regarding Master Nangong's proposal
to mobilize the forces of Yiqi Alliance
and attack Nanchui.
Young Master, here's a report!
Esteemed family masters,
Nanchui Poison King
sent someone to deliver a letter of surrender.
[Letter of Surrender]
Demons are always cunning and dangerous by nature.
It's too late for them
to surrender now.
They also sent this item
along with the surrender letter.
It's the Hundred-Eyed Demon Lord's demon core.
The Hundred-Eyed Demon Lord already offered his demon core.
Let's end this matter here.
[Nangong's residence, Yiqi Alliance]
Master Nangong,
are we really
going to listen to that Wangquan brat?
Didn't you hear what Young Master Wangquan said?
The Poison King already submitted the Hundred-Eyed Demon Lord's demon core.
If our Yiqi Alliance still not lets it go,
it will cause chaos among the demons
and inevitably bring disaster upon ourselves.
Wangquan Hongye,
he ruined my big plan.
The Hundred-Eyed Demon Lord's demon core
came at such a perfect time. That's weird.
Indeed,
perfect timing. So fishy.
Our Young Master Wangquan
is like the sky,
seemingly peaceful and clear,
yet hiding storms and gathering clouds.
The Nangong family is not holding sway over the Yiqi Alliance.
If this little brat, Hongye, doesn't obey,
we can just kill him.
Has anyone ever told you that
Miss Dongfang looks gorgeous when preparing tea?
the Yang family's young lady who doesn't drink
speaks in a strange way?
I've told you that I'm under the weather lately.
What?
Are you upset because I don't drink with you at night?
Yang Yan,
you're not acting like yourself.
Every time I see how harmonious your family is,
I feel so envious.
And the food at your home is especially palatable
with a homey vibe.
Did you come all the way here
to meet me today
just to beat around the bush with me?
I'm here just to visit you today.
Did
something happen to Mu Xiaowu?
Or does your father not allow you
to date him because he's poor?
If my father disliked him,
I would just leave with him.
Well...
Xiaowu...
What happened to him?
When he was supervising in the mine,
he let a little demon escape in a moment of weakness.
Someone reported this to the Yiqi Alliance.
Xiaowu...
He was taken away by the Inspection Bureau.
The Nangong family holds sway over the Inspection Bureau alone,
using it to coerce the other major families
and the Wangquan Manor.
Our Yang family has little influence.
Even my father's intervention can't help him.
I'm worried that, in a place like the Inspection Bureau...
There must be a way out.
There must be a way.
Yeah, there must be a way.
I didn't plan to bring this up
when I came to meet you today.
It'd only make you worry.
I just don't know if I'll...
If you don't want me to check your pulse,
just tell me
the real reason why you
can't drink.
I'm carrying Xiaowu's child.
Other family masters are dissatisfied with the Wangquans.
They want me to take over.
Wangquan Shouzhuo has been missing for a long time.
That coward, Wangquan Hongye, is nowhere near
qualified to lead the Yiqi Alliance.
He is a coward?
Ever since he took over the Yiqi Alliance,
the Wangquan Sword has never been drawn even once.
If that's not cowardice, what is?
Our Nangong family is gaining ground right now.
You should seize the chance and make a decisive move!
The unsheathed sword doesn't necessarily mean cowardice.
It's more likely that
he wants to deal a fatal blow.
This demon sword
will be completed in ten days.
When the time comes, I will host a night banquet.
I will invite Wangquan Hongye
and the major families to it.
You mean to trap them?
The fire in this furnace is not fierce enough now.
Remember,
only despair will make this fire burn stronger.
Be it humans or demons,
they all have something foolish that they can't let go of.
It's emotion.
This is their weakness.
I got it.
I'll go arrange it right away.
As for Wangquan Hongye,
I will pay a visit to the Divine Fire Villa.
In this world, only the Divine Fire can counter the Wangquan Sword.
Father, aren't you afraid that after getting rid of the wolf,
we might face a tiger again?
The Divine Fire Villa has been in seclusion for years
with a great reputation
but no real power.
Inviting the Divine Fire out
will surely guarantee our victory.
I want everyone in the world to see that
Dongfang Divine Fire
is siding with our Nangong family.
Huaizhu!
Where's Miss Yang?
She left.
Huaizhu,
you look kind of depressed. What's up?
As you know,
Yang Yan is my only friend
in Yiqi Alliance.
Of course I know that.
You've told me before.
You two were classmates when you were young.
She's as lovely as warm jade.
All this time,
I've believed that
the Divine Fire Villa's seclusion from the world,
our family's harmony,
and giving up fame and fortune
were all the right choices.
But now,
we're far from the Yiqi Alliance,
and I can't even help my best friend.
So, Qinlan,
is there really
a utopia in this world?
Miss Huaizhu, we have a visitor.
He claimed to be the Master of the Nangong family
and specifically asked to see you, Miss Huaizhu.
Nangong Ye?
The Inspection Bureau?
Mr. Nangong.
Sir, what brings you
here today?
Please feel free to speak.
Miss Dongfang, you're quite straightforward.
There's indeed something I'd like to discuss with you.
The Yiqi Alliance is deeply corrupted.
The blame lies with the Wangquan family.
I am determined to replace them.
I humbly request your assistance, Miss Dongfang,
in capturing and killing Wangquan Hongye.
Mr. Nangong,
what can I get
if I help you?
As long as we can bring down the Wangquans,
I can give you
whatever you need.
Young Master, you just rejected Nangong Ye's proposal to attack Nanchui,
so he's now holding a grand sword-opening ceremony.
At this ceremony,
he will surely propose to promote using demon cores in sword forging.
If you reject it again,
it will be openly making an enemy of the Nangongs.
We are already enemies.
It's just making the hostility aboveboard.
Will you go attend it, Young Master?
For the treacherous banquet in ten days,
inform Zui to bring Yang Yitan along
and go attend it with me.